mobomarket.net 2016-06-26

# Privacy Policy - Mobomarket

This privacy policy applies to your use of our mobile application. By downloading or using our App, you agree that your information, including your personal information, will be handled as described in this Privacy Policy. This Policy incorporates by reference our Mobomarket [User Agreement](http://www.mobomarket.net/agreement.html); your use of our App and any disputes you may have regarding our App and our use of your personal information will be governed by our Mobomarket User Agreement.

### Information We Collect About You

In order to help us understand our users' trends and needs, and to improve the quality of our services, we may collect:

  * User behavior data, which include the time you spent on our App, the features you were using, the apps that you clicked, installations, clicks and gestures.
  * Data relative to users’ activity rate, App retention study, uninstall rate as technical support so that we can optimize the quality of our App.
  * Detailed download log to help locate user’s problems from user feedbacks, such as slow in download or fail to download.
  * Information about user’s mobile devices, which include phone models, resolution, memory space, to help us better adapt our App to different mobile phones.

Other installed apps information, which include apps and their using frequency, in order to recommend users personalized content

In order to participate in some activities, we may ask you to create a user name and password and/or to provide other, non-personal information such as your age, date of birth, gender, and/or game and platform preferences; and, combine such information with your personal information.

You will be responsible for any consequences arising from problems caused by the provision of untruthful and/or, inaccurate Information. Please do not transfer or lend your account name or password to any third party. On the internet, a user’s account name or password may be used illegally as a result of hacking or otherwise or the user’s own negligence in protecting such information. Please notify Baidu (Hong Kong) Limited immediately if you find that your account has been illegally used by others any third party.

When you submit your Information, it shall be deemed as your consent to the collection, storage, use and/or disclosure of the Information by us. We may use the Information to improve our products and/or services.

### How We Use Your Information

We use your Information for the following purposes:

  * To provide our App and our services to you;
  * To respond to your requests, including your customer service inquiries;
  * For marketing and advertising purposes through various marketing channels, including, without limitation, sending you promotional emails, advertising our services on third party sites and social media platforms, direct mail, and App ads. We may use the Information we collect about you and other targeting criteria to identify a range of goods and services that may be of interest to you. These offers may include targeted special offers for goods and services tailored to you that are offered by us;
  * To understand how you use our App (including features used most frequently), and to improve our App and our services;
  * If you opt-in, to send you push notifications;
  * For research and analytics;
  * As elsewhere described in this policy;
  * As we may notify you from time to time;
  * As permitted by law; and
  * With your consent.

Baidu will manage your Information with care and will not publicly disclose such Information or provide such Information to any third party aside from Baidu affiliated companies without your prior authorization. By downloading the App, you hereby further acknowledge, accept and grant your consent to Baidu to disclose your Information to Baidu affiliated companies or on a strictly-need to know basis to any reliable contractor of Baidu or to any other third parties who provides the same level of care as Baidu to protect your information.

### Sharing Your Information

We do not sell your Information to non-affiliated third parties for their own marketing purposes. We may share your Information, including information that we collect directly from you, information that we collect about you from third parties, and information that we collect automatically, for the following purposes and with the following persons/entities:

  * Service providers: such as entities that assist us with consulting, marketing, advertising, information technology, App usage analytics, and any other services that we use in our operations;
  * To affiliated entities: our affiliates may combine your information with information that they collect about you. Our affiliates may use your information (whether alone, combined with other information, or in the aggregate) for their everyday business purposes; to market products and services to you (including through email); and to develop products or services;
  * To our business partners: where necessary to fulfill your request of yours or where you consent, we may share your information with our business partners;
  * To law enforcement, government representatives or others where required by law;
  * In connection with the sale, purchase, merger, or reorganization;
  * When we believe it is necessary to protect the rights, property, safety of us or to comply with a judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process, or as evidence in litigation in which we are involved;
  * We also may share aggregate information about our users with third parties, including for various marketing purposes; and
  * To protect the legitimate rights and interests of Baidu, such as to search, prevent and/or address fraud or security-related problems.

Baidu shall not be responsible for any collection, disclosure or use of your Information provided by you to any third party’s website that may be linked to or from Baidu’s website or to the App.

### Transfer of Personal Data

Please be informed that your personal data may be transferred to locations outside of the territory where you are accessing Baidu’s services or disclosed to our related corporations, licensees, business partners and/or service providers for the purposes described above.

### Security

We encrypt our services and data transmission using SSL. We strive at all times to ensure that your personal data will be protected against unauthorized or accidental access, processing, correction or deletion. We implement appropriate security measures to safeguard and secure your personal data. Please note, however, that no security measures are 100% effective. We encourage you to take measures to protect your personal data.

You are responsible for maintaining the privacy and the confidentiality of Information. Please keep yourself informed when accessing the internet and to always read and review the policy / privacy statement on the site that you are accessing. Please ensure that you do the following: (i) not to disclose your password, (ii) not to provide any personal information to anyone, including their names, (iii) never fill online forms without your prior authorization. Please use complex passwords with long enough combinations of letters and numbers that require unusual keyboard combinations whereas; simple passwords are easy to be broken. Please never give your password to anyone online. In any event, please change your password periodically.

### Intellectual Property Rights

All text, data, images, graphics, audio and/or video information and other materials within the App are the property of Baidu and duly protected by copyright, trademark and/or other property rights laws. Nothing in this policy shall be construed as conferring any license of any intellectual property rights or such materials by Baidu to you. You are prohibited from copying, displaying, downloading, modifying, reproducing or creating any derivative works of such App materials, directly or indirectly published, performed, rewritten or republished, or otherwise used for commercial purposes without prior written consent from Baidu.

### Privacy Policy Amendment

Baidu may amend its Policy from time to time. If there are any significant changes to the Policy, we will post the relevant rules in a prominent place on our web page so as to notify users in a timely fashion or by obtaining consent as may otherwise be required.

### Language

This Policy is made in the English and the Indonesian languages and the Parties agree that in the event of any inconsistency between the English and the Indonesian language versions, then the English language version shall prevail and take precedence.

### Questions and Suggestions

If you have any questions or suggestions, please contact us at [[isth@baidu.com](mailto:isth@baidu.com)].
